# Debadutta Gourav

# Sn. Frontend Specialist

Pune, Maharashtra +91 - 8169713953 / 9158920775 dqourav 1992@qmail.com

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Front End professional with more than 7 years of experience in software and 4.5 years in Javascript Fullstack .Great team player with excellent communication skills.Always writes high quality code and has an eye for design. Uptodate with latest technology and trends in the field of front end development technologies like Angular , Node js and other javascript frameworks.Always willing to learn and master new technologies and languages.

Currently serving my notice period. Last day of working is 7th Oct 2021.

# **SKILLS**

#### **TECHNICAL**

- FrontEnd Angular 2+,HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript,Typescript
- Backend Python, Node. js
- Tools Visual Studio Code, Git, Putty, Jenkins
- Database MySQL,MySQL Lite,Cloud Firestore, MongoDB
- Cloud AWS

### **WORK**

- Good Time Management
- Team Player
- Excellent Communication skills
- Design oriented
- High Quality code

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Infosys Limited, Pune** - Systems Engineer

MAY 2014 - DEC 2016

### • Ebanking Development project for Standard Bank Nigeria

I worked on the development of different Ebanking modules like Payments, Beneficiary Management, UI development etc for the client. It involved working in Finacle comprising Java, Angular and SQL database.

## • Mbanking Support project for Standard Bank Nigeria

Worked on client location(i.e Lagos, Nigeria) for two months to provide onsite client support during the deployment of the Mbanking system. I was working in a two member team directly interacting with the client.

# • Mbanking Development project for Standard Bank , Africa

Worked in development of various Mbanking modules for Multi country Mbanking projects.

#### Client support project for Mobile Banking(Standard Bank)

Worked in client location(i.e Johannesburg,SA) for 3 months to provide support for mobile banking of 6 African countries.

#### • Client support and Development project for MBanking(Kotak Bank)

Worked in client location(i.e Mumbai) for 3 months to do development and provide Mbanking support for Kotak Bank.lt involved working in Finacle comprising Java, Angular and SQL database.

# Freelancer, Pune - Web Developer

JAN 2017 - MARCH 2018

- Two apps published in the play store and many other demo apps build.
- Helped many small clients to debug/launch their websites and android apps.

# Devworkx Labs, Raipur- Full Stack Developer

APRIL 2018 - FEB 2020

#### GRPBAZAAR.COM

Provided end to end technical solution for a hyperlocal grocery delivery platform. We ran the services along with a team of 6.

#### Matchless Dentist(https://matchlessdentist.com/)

Provided end to end technical solution for a dental products delivery platform

### • Waterboyz.in(https://admin.waterboyz.in/)

Admin Panel in Angular for a water delivery service. Features include Invoice Management and Reporting System.

### • Kanchan Medico(https://admin.kanchanmedico.com/)

Admin Panel in Angular for an in-house drug order service. Features include creating and deleting invoices, Inventory Management and Reporting System.

#### Voda Water(<u>https://admin.voda.co.ke/</u>)

Voda water delivery project for a client in Kenya. Made Admin Panel in Angular to manage products, deliveries, sales etc.

#### Prelytic Pharma(<u>https://app.xpressrx.co/</u>)

Full stack Medicine Management Software for Retailers to manage stocks, Sales, purchases and Availability .Made using Angular and Node.js

#### Spah Project

- Admin: <a href="https://spah-dev.web.app/">https://spah-dev.web.app/</a>
- User:<u>https://www.spah.in/</u>

Spah.in is a marketplace for spa services. We are currently working on an admin panel for super admins and for Spa Shop Owners. We also developed a Front end website for end users in javascript and html and currently working on a web app in Angular.

# **Engagely.ai, Pune** - Frontend Specialist

FEB 2020 - PRESENT

 Working as a frontend specialist on core products - Livechat, Admin Panel and Chabot.

# **EDUCATION**

Silicon Institute of Technology, Bhubaneswar - B.Tech(Computer Science)

AUG 2010 - JULY 2014